UNITE Legislative Department Audio-Visual Materials 6000/007 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Legislative Department Audio-Visual Materials
1989-2001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
6000/007 AV
2.67 cubic feet
2.7 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
5748437
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 01, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000/007: UNITE Legislative Department Records
Textile industry--New York (State)--New York; Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York; Clothing trade--New York (State)--New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives.; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees --Archives.; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Legislative Dept.; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
5748437
- UNITE "Words", 1 (Box 1)
- BCTD National Conference 97: Al Gore, Vice President, 2 (Box 1)
- Ellis Island: Medals of Honor Awards Gala; May 16, 1993, 3 (Box 1)
- Unlabeled, 4 (Box 1)
- Ask Congress: Guarino - Dubrow - McHugh, 5 (Box 1)
- Behind the labels: Garment Workers in US: Saipan, 6 (Box 1)
- National Education Association; National Advertising Campaign; Fall 2001, 7 (Box 1)
- UNITE "Guess who pockets the difference?", 8 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Part 1: English; Part 2: Spanish
- Sen. Commerce - GATT, 1994; 9 (Box 1)
  tape #1
- Sen. Commerce - GATT, 1994; 10 (Box 1)
  Tape #2
- Apparel Jobs Abroad, 1992; 11 (Box 1)
  WCBS TV Channel 2 -- 60 Minutes
- Prison Work Program, 12 (Box 1)
- NBC Dateline: Sweatshops Segment: June 4, 1996, 13 (Box 1)
- Sweatshops, 14 (Box 1)
  Dateline, NBC-TV Network
- 60 Minutes Segment: "One Child's Labor" with Craig Keilberger, 1996; 15 (Box 1)
  April 1996
- 60 Minutes - Prison Labor, 16 (Box 1)
- Sweatshops - Rough Cut #2, 17 (Box 1)
- Behind the Seems: 60 Minutes, 1994; 18 (Box 1)
  WCBS TV (CBS) - December 11, 1994
- Convention of Union of Needletrades, industrial and Textile Employees, AFL-CIO, CLC, 1995; 19 (Box 1)
  Miami Beach, Florida: June 29-30, 1995
- Surviving the bottom line with Hedrick Smith, 20 (Box 1)
- Jay Mazur / Rain Fair, 1991; 21 (Box 1)
  Evening News
- Rep. Maurice Hinchey, 22 (Box 1)
- Hillary Clinton Sews Union Label, 1996; 23 (Box 1)
  3/6/1996 New York City
- Evy Dubrow Roast, February 26, 1997, 24 (Box 1)
- Is there a sweatshop in your future?, 25 (Box 1)
  English/Spanish
- Evy: a roast of Evelyn Dubrow, 1997; 26 (Box 1)
- 2000 United States Hispanic Leadership Conference, 27 (Box 1)
- ILGWU, Evelyn Dubrow Roast, 1989; 28 (Box 1)
  May 4, 1989
- Evy Duty: 5/3/1989, 29 (Box 1)
- Fashion Industry Forum: July 16, 1996, Marymount University, 30 (Box 1)
- IAM Power Chain, 31 (Box 1)
- COPE: the 1996 conventions: Let's be there: Pre-Primary Caucus, 32 (Box 1)
- UNITE!: Because every vote counts, 33 (Box 1)
- An Interview with Evelyn Dubrow and Jesse Calhoon, 34 (Box 1)
- Barney Frankly on E.N.D.A.; narrated by Pat Schroeder, 35 (Box 1)
- Committee of 100, 36 (Box 1)
- Unlabeled, 1 (Box 2)
- Unlabeled, 2 (Box 2)
- The GAP in Guatemala: behind the Gates of Shin Won, 3 (Box 2)
- Television Advertisement in Opposition to Africa Growth and Opportunity Act, 4 (Box 2)
- What happened to the American dream?, 5 (Box 2)
  Political Action Video - UNITE
- No pain, more gain: What the C.A.F. fund can do for you, 6 (Box 2)
  English version
- The Long March of Newt Gingrich, 1996; 7 (Box 2)
  Frontline, PBS-TV network 1/16/1996
- UPN 9 News; Evelyn Dubrow/Kenar Sweatshops, 8 (Box 2)
- Northeastern Illinois University/UNITE: Partners in Progress: the Worker Education Program, 9 (Box 2)
- FOX Morning News; 6/28/1996, 10 (Box 2)
- What Happened to the American Dream?, 11 (Box 2)
  Political Action Video
- We do the work; Show 309; Sewing our future, 12 (Box 2)
- Newspaper Roundtable, 1998; 13 (Box 2)
  Purdue University Public Affairs Video Archives
- Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee: Medicare Ad, 1995; 14 (Box 2)
- Faith and Politics, 15 (Box 2)
- The Spirit of 7 gbal, 16 (Box 2)
  Solidarity Kids Theater, Minneapolis/St. Paul
- ILGWU; Apparel Job, 1992; 17 (Box 2)
  WABC-TV Channel 7; Nightline, Sept. 30, 1992; Maidenform, WABC-TV Channel 7, Nightline, Sept 29, 1992
- Solidarity Kids Theater 1996, 18 (Box 2)
- Prison Blues on We do the Work, PBS (April 1995), 19 (Box 2)
- Carib Nation #411, 20 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Dept of Labor, Hall of Fame, 1993, 21 (Box 2)
- Hidden Heroes: Youth Activism in the 90's, 22 (Box 2)
- The Harry S. Truman Library Institute: Twenty First Century Fund, 23 (Box 2)
- The Humphrey Campaign: National Press Club, #28, 24 (Box 2)
  film
- For every NPR story: Children's Day on the Hill (Box 3)
- President Harry S. Truman, Vice President Alben W. Barkley, Secretary of Labor Maurice J. Tobin (Box 4)
- The Eastern Shuffle: songs for the Eastern Picketline (Box 5)
- Whiteville Apparel Choir together (Box 6)
- ILGWU 1948 Campaign Committee; Truman, Barklay, and Labor (Box 7)
- ILGWU 1948 Campaign Committee; Truman, Barklay and Labor (Box 8)
  Ronald Reagan